Quirini, Helen; Papers apap102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Community Activism, 1898-2010; Undated; 6
  - Health Care, 1969-2009; Undated; 6.8; 4.0 cubic ft.
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, News Clippings, 2006 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, News Clippings, 2007 January-2007 June (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, News Clippings, 2007 July-2007 December (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, News Clippings, 2008 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, News Clippings, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Berger Commission Affects on Schenectady Hospitals, St. Clare's Hospital Publications, 2007 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Berger Commission Legislation and Facts, 2006-2007; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - Carver Community Health Center, Pamphlets, Fliers, Leaflets, Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - Citizen Action of New York, Fliers and News Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - "Communities Working Together for a Healthier New York," Report to the Commissioner of Health, New York State Public Health Council, 1996 September (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, Ombudsman Plan, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Assemblyman Paul Tonko, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Congressman Michael McNulty, 2007 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - "County of Schenectady Proposed Public Health System", 1990 June 29 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Draft of Presidential Health Reform Proposal, 1993 September (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Enhancing and Sustaining Informal Support Networks, Pamphlet, 1981 November (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Family Respite Co-Op Handbook, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - GE Retirees, HMOs and Health Care, 1988-1993 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, "An Analysis of the Administration's Health Proposal," Congressional Budget Office, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Public Forum, 1993 November 15 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Public Forum, 1993 November 22 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Report to Governor, 1994 January 05 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Testimony of the Medical Society of the State of New York, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Testimony of Murray Nusbaum, MD, 1993 November 22 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Testimony of the New York State Nurses Association, 1993 November 15 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Testimony from the Town Meetings on President Clinton's Health Care Plan, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, Text of Affordable Health Care Now Act, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - Health Care Leaflets and Pamphlets, Health Care Reform, Long Term Care, Medications, 1979-1992 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - Health Care Action Line, Appalachia-Mohawk Subarea Council, 1977-1981 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43)
    - Health Care Action Line, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 44)
    - Health Care Action Line, Directions and Guidelines, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 45)
    - Health Care Action Line, Incoming Call Log, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 46)
    - Health Care Action Line, News Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 47)
    - Health Care Action Line, Notes and Call Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 48)
    - Health Care Action Line, Ombudsman Committee, Meeting Agendas, Minutes and Reports, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 49)
    - Health Care Action Line, Outgoing Call Log, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 50)
    - Health Care Action Line, Reference Material, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - Health Care Action Line, Referral Phone Number List, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - "Health Care Cost Containment" Conference, Reports, Program, 1978 June 05 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - Health Care Issues Committee, News Clippings, 1987 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - Health Care Reform Task Force, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - Health Care Reform Task Force, Information, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - Health Care Reform Task Force, Minutes, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - Health Care Reform Task Force, Training Program Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - "Health Management in the Seventies" Conference, Correspondence, Press Releases, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Ad Hoc Long Term Care Workgroup, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Agency Closure, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Aging and Long Term Care Report, 1980 October 29 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Analysis of Need for Long Term Care Beds, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Annual Action Plan, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Annual Reports, 1976-1981; 1983-1984; 1986-1987; 1990-1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Baptist Retirement Center, Report, Memorandum and Budget, 1991; 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Board of Director and Address Lists, 1976; 1990; 1993-1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Board of Directors Orientation Kit, 1978 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Budgets and Treasurer's Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Correspondence, 1972; 1977; 1989-1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, High Peaks Hospice, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, House Democratic Health Care Bill, Reports, 1994 August (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, HSA/NENY News, 1977-1979; 1984; 1987-1990 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Long Term Care Reports, 1990; 1993 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for May 14, 1976 First Annual Meeting Correspondence, Memorandum, Minutes, 1976 April-1976 June (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for June 6, 1988 Board of Directors Meeting, Leaflet, Memorandum, Agenda, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1988 April-1988 June (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for June 1, 1992 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Clipping, Agendas, Reports, Correspondence, 1992 April-1992 June (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for August 3, 1992 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Memorandum, Reports, J, 1993 July-1993 August (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for September 14, 1992 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda Memorandum, Reports, 1992 August-1992 September (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for November 2, 1992 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Reports, Memorandum, Minutes, 1992 October-1992 November (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for December 7, 1992 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Agenda, Reports, 1992 October-1992 December (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for January 4, 1993 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Minutes, Memorandum, Correspondence, 1992 December-1993 February (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for March 1, 1993 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Reports, 1993 February-1993 March (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for June 6, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Memorandum, 1994 May-1994 June (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for August 2, 1993 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Reports, Agendas, News Clippings, 1993 August (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for September 13, 1993 Executive Committee Meeting, Correspondence, Minutes, Memorandum, Report, 1993 July-1993 September (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for October 3, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Memorandum, Reports, Correspondence, 1994 July-1994 October (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for November 1, 1993 Executive Committee Meeting, Minutes, Memorandum, Reports, 1993 October-1993 November (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for February 7, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Minutes, Memorandum, Reports, 1994 January-1994 February (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for April 4, 1994 Board of Directors Meeting, Agenda, Minutes, Memorandum, Reports, Correspondence, 1994 March-1994 April (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for April 4, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Memorandum, Reports, 1994 March-1994 April (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for March 7, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1994 February-1994 March (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for May 2, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Minutes, Memorandum, Reports, Correspondence, 1994 April-1994 May (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for May 20, 1994 Health Care Reform Task Force Meeting, Agendas, Correspondence, Reports, 1994 February-1994 May (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 44)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for August 1, 1994 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Reports, Correspondence, 1994 July-1994 August (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 45)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for February 6, 1995 Executive Committee Meeting, Memorandum, Reports, Correspondence, 1995 January-1995 February (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 46)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for April 3, 1995 Executive Committee Meeting, Agenda, Correspondence, Memorandum, Reports, 1995 February-1995 April (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 47)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Materials for September 11, 1995 Board of Directors Meeting, Agendas, Memorandum, Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1995 April-1995 September (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 48)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1976-1979; 1981; 1993-1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 49)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Memorandum, 1977-1978; 1988-1989; 1992-1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 50)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Miscellaneous Documents, 1987; 1993-1997 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Miscellaneous Publications, 1980; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, News Clippings, 1989; 1992-1994 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Northeastern New York HIV Care Network, Newsletters, Flyers, Membership Lists and Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Orientation Kit, 1990 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Plan for HIV/AIDS Services in Northeastern New York, Report, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Planning Area Profiles, 1994 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Policies and By-Laws, 1992-1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Project Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Reports, 1978; 1980; 1990-1993 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Review and Comment Records, 1978; 1980; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Review Material, 1977; 1980; 1985 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, State of New York Department of Health Minimum Standards for Hospitals, 1988 August 22 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Sunnyview Hospital and Rehabilitation Center, Reports and Memorandum, 1993 July (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Warren County Hospices, Memorandums, Minutes, Correspondence and Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Health Systems Agency of Northeastern New York, Warren County Hospices, State Health Department Review, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Healthy Capital District Initiative, "Health Profile: Report to Sponsors", 1997 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Healthy Capital District Initiative, Healthy Capital District Initiative Survey, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Hilltop Manor, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - HMOs, Agendas, Articles, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - HMO Governing Board Handbook, 1980 September (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - Lobby Day for New York Health, Fliers, Correspondence, 1992 June 09 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - Local Health Care Issues Core Group, Long Term Care, Correspondence, Reports and News Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - Long Term Care, Leaflets, Pamphlets, News Clippings, Reports and Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - "Meeting the Home Health Care Needs of the Elderly in the 21st Century Through Telecommunication", 1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, Administrative Services Proposal, 1981 November 18 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, Board of Director and Physician Lists, 1981-1983 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, Budgets, 1983 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, By-Laws and Policy, 1981-1983 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, Contract and Certificate of Incorporation, 1981 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Mohawk Valley Physician's Health Plan, Leaflets and Publications, 1981-1983 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - National Health Care Reform, Articles and News Clippings, 1984; 1988; 1990-1997 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - National Health Care Reform, Pamphlets and Fliers, 1990-1997 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - National Health Care Reform, Reports and Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - "A New Yorker's Guide to Health Insurance Choices," New York State Office of the Aging, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - New York Health Care Reform, News Clippings, Fliers, Articles, Correspondence, Reports, 1989-1995 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - New York Health Care Reform, Signed Petitions, 1992 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Notes on Health Care, 2007-2008; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - "The Organization and Delivery of Home Care Services", Report, 1984 December (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - President Clinton's Health Security Plan, Fliers, Posters, Bumper Stickers, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - President Clinton's Health Security Plan, News Clippings, Fact Sheets, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43)
    - President Clinton's Health Security Plan, Summary of Key Changes, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 44)
    - Primary Care Restructuring Committee Work Groups, 2008 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - Public Health Services in Schenectady County, Report, 1989 May (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - "Reimbursement in 1980: Issues and Choices" Conference, Agenda, Reports, 1980 September 09 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - Republican Health Care Task Force Draft Staff Proposal, 1993 September (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - Rights of Patients, Hospitals and Funerals, 1990; 1999; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Ambulance Case, 1988 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Anti-Smoking Committee, Minutes, News Clippings and Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 1988; 1993; 1996; 1998-1999 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2000 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2001 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2002 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2005 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, 2006-2008 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Binder of Minutes and Supplemental Materials, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Establishment of Schenectady County Health Department, 1974; 1987-1990 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Handwritten Notes, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Health Assessment Reports, 1988 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1994-1998 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Ombudsman Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, News Clippings, Articles, 1988-1996 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Notes, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Phone and Address Lists, 1987; 1990 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Publications, Flyers, Pamphlets, 1986-1989; 1997-1998 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Schenectady County Committee on Health Care Issues, Testimonies, 1986-1989 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Schenectady County Community Health Assessment, 1989 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Schenectady County Public Health Services, Health Beat, 1991 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Schenectady Free Health Clinic, Arnold Ritterband, 1993-2008; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - Schenectady Free Health Clinic, Correspondence, Notes, 2001-2007 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - Schenectady Free Health Clinic, News Clippings, 1999; 2002-2003; 2005; 2007 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - Schenectady League of Women Voters, 2006-2007 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - Schenectady Regional Health Center Project, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)